Well, it's okay.  We will also have to wait for the results.
Our colleague Harsh has already
given this estimate.  There has been decent attraction in the last six months.
Returns of up to 15.5% have been seen here.  How do
you like this space?
SBI definitely has very attractive charts.
It has a cup and handle formation
on a larger degree.  If we say large degree then a
very
strong trend has been formed in the weekly charts.  Cup end handle is the
fashion of the handle.
We are seeing a consolidation breakout.  If
you look at the data of last six months, then almost this stock was
stuck in the range of 1750 to 1850.
Now today it is quite well placed above 1850.
And I think yes,
we may see breakouts in this.  And
we will see a momentum rally catching up with significant volumes.  On the
upside,
levels of 1950 to 2000 open.  So
definitely it is a buy call from my end
and my view is definitely bullish.  On the downside, as
long as the 1800 levels are intact,
for a short period of time the view will remain positive.   So
let's take a positive view here, an
interesting pattern is
visible in SBI Life.  We will also tell you all the important things about the results
when they come.
Anyway, we will stop here for a short while as I Life
's September quarter results are out.
Our colleague
Harsh has joined to tell us how the results will be.  Yes Harsh, tell us what
are your estimates regarding the results of SBI Life?   Yes.
So the top line number is what is
called annualized premium equivalent in life insurance terms.  This will
grow around single digit.  The only thing is that during the 3 to 4%
growth, when we
talk about this growth, your
GST rate cuts have now come and now
SBI Life has got only eight days in the September quarter to show the impact of those GST rate
cuts to the customers,
so the growth may increase and the pace of growth may
increase going forward, so we will see this thing
from the management commentary, what is
their opinion.  Are they
seeing growth increasing at the ground level or not
?  So this will be the first
thing which will be most important.  But
broad growth is
not expected this quarter.  That APE number will grow around 3 and 1/2%.  The
second
thing happened was VNB.  What is VNB right now?
Value of New Business
is basically a metric of profitability
in life insurance.  So, the most important thing is how profitable
business they are bringing.
This will
grow around 5% on a yearly basis.  So the
profitability or margin will increase a little
because of this.  Currently the margin guidance was
26 to 28%.  The margin number will
come around 27.2%.  There will be a close watch on the bank channel
because SBI can push
SBI Life products through the bank channel, that is, through its own bank customers. The
kind of traction it is getting will be
another very important thing
that will be in the minds of investors.
So we have to assess these four things.  But
when the basic numbers come, the focus will be on the margin numbers.
If margins reach 27.2% and
growth is around 3.5%, then the
Street will be quite okay with SBI Life's
numbers.
Thank you Harsh for
clearly explaining all the things regarding SBI Life results prediction.
Ah